1. comment("Story: Login to CURA system")
5. comment("Given that the user has the valid login information")
9. openBrowser(G_SiteURL)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. click(findTestObject("Page_CuraHomepage/btn_MakeAppointment"))
21. takeElementScreenshotAsCheckpoint("Login Dialog Origin", LoginObject)
25. setText(findTestObject("Page_Login/txt_UserName"), Username)
29. setText(findTestObject("Page_Login/txt_Password"), Password)
33. takeElementScreenshotAsCheckpoint("Login Dialog With Data", LoginObject)
37. comment("When he logins to CURA system")
41. click(findTestObject("Page_Login/btn_Login"))
45. comment("Then he should be able to login successfully")
49. landingPage = verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/div_Appointment"), G_Timeout)
53. closeBrowser()
1. cleanup()